Courage echoes forever.
Paradise Road is a war, drama, history film directed by Bruce Beresford.
A group of English, American, Dutch and Australian women creates a vocal orchestra while
being imprisoned in a Japanese POW camp on Sumatra during World War II.
Adrienne Pargiter, played by Glenn Close.
Dr. Verstak, played by Frances McDormand.
Daisy 'Margaret' Drummond, played by Pauline Collins.
Susan Macarthy, played by Cate Blanchett.
Topsy Merritt, played by Julianna Margulies.
Rosemary Leighton-Jones, played by Jennifer Ehle.
Paradise Road is a 1997 Australian war film directed by Bruce Beresford, about a group of English, American,
Dutch, and Australian women who are imprisoned by the Japanese in Sumatra during World War II.
It stars Glenn Close, Frances McDormand, Pauline Collins, Julianna
Margulies, Jennifer Ehle, Cate Blanchett, and Elizabeth Spriggs.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of prison, island,
singapore, world war ii, prisoner of war.
The tone is emotional.